Register to The Quincy Porter Papers
Yale University Music Library
- Correspondence, Series I
  - General Correspondence, I.A
    - To Porter, from Individuals, I.A.1
      - Fairchild, Blair (Box 1, Folder 11)
        No date -- 2 cards (scrapbook)
      - Falcão, Ildefonso (Box 1, Folder 11)
        1943 May 6 -- typed letter signed (scrapbook)
      - Farrar, John (Box 1, Folder 11)
        1959 -- 2 typed letters signed
      - Farrer, Edward (Box 1, Folder 12)
        1949 Jun 13 -- autograph letter signed
        1949 Mar 1 -- typed letter signed
      - Fassett, James (Box 1, Folder 12)
        1940? Nov 24 -- telegram
      - [Feinzimer, Saml ?] (Box 1, Folder 12)
        1950 -- 2 autograph letters signed
      - Feist, Leonard (Box 1, Folder 12)
        See: Mercury Music Corp.; Music Publishers' Association
      - Fennell, Frederick (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - Fetler, Paul (Box 1, Folder 12)
        1948-1949 -- 3 autograph letters signed
      - Fiedler, Arthur (Box 1, Folder 12)
        1943 Nov 14 -- autograph letter signed (scrapbook)
      - Fine, Vivian (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - Finney, Ross Lee (Box 1, Folder 12)
        1947-1950 -- 2 typed letters signed
        See also: Yaddo; Valley Music Press
      - Fish, Arnold (Box 1, Folder 12)
        See: Juilliard School of Music
      - Fisher, Bob (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - Fisher, Paul G. (Box 1, Folder 12)
        1949 Nov 24 -- autograph letter signed (scrapbook)
      - Fogel, Henry (Box 1, Folder 12)
        1966 Mar 25 -- typed letter signed
      - Fohrman, Sherwood E. (Box 1, Folder 12)
        1964 Sep 22 -- typed letter signed
      - Forbes, Arthur W. (Box 1, Folder 12)
        1963 -- 2 autograph letters signed
      - Fordyce, Nancy H. (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - Forte, Allen (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - Foster, Eleanor (Box 1, Folder 12)
        1946 Dec 7 -- typed letter signed
      - Frank, Anita (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - Franke, Roberta Felty (Box 1, Folder 12)
        1959 Apr 12 -- autograph letter signed
      - Freed, Isadore (Box 1, Folder 12)
        No year Jan 31 -- autograph letter signed
        1956 -- 2 typed letters signed
      - French, Richard F. (Box 1, Folder 12)
        1959 Aug 19 -- typed letter signed
        See also: Associated Music Publishers, Inc.; Harvard University
      - [Frey, Nadae ?] (Box 1, Folder 12)
        No year Mar 30 -- autograph letter signed (scrapbook)
      - Frost, Bernice (Box 1, Folder 13)
        No year Feb 20 -- autograph letter signed
      - Frost, Katherine (Box 1, Folder 13)
        1939 Aug 5 -- typed letter signed
      - Frost, Robert (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - Frulla, Guelfo Angelo (Box 1, Folder 13)
        1959 Nov 15 -- autograph letter signed
      - Fuchs, Joseph (Box 1, Folder 13)
        No date -- card
      - Furman, Arlie (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - Gabriel, Cris (Mrs. Ralph H.) (Box 1, Folder 13)
        1964 Feb 18 -- autograph letter signed
      - Gates, Bill (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - Geer, E. Harold (Box 1, Folder 13)
        1938 Apr 2 -- telegram (scrapbook)
      - Geraci, Filippo P. (Box 1, Folder 13)
        1965 Apr 27 -- typed letter signed
      - Gerstel, Martin (Box 1, Folder 13)
        1966 Feb 7 -- autograph letter signed
      - Getman, Christopher (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - Gibbs, Robert (Box 1, Folder 13)
        1933 Jan 14 -- autograph letter signed (scrapbook)
      - Gideon, Miriam (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - Gifford, Norman (Box 1, Folder 13)
        1934-1938 -- 3 autograph letters signed (1-scrapbook)
        1938 Jun 27 -- typed letter signed
      - Giles, Allen (Box 1, Folder 13)
        See: University of Buffalo
      - Gillis, Albert (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - Gillis, Albert (Box 1, Folder 13)
        1949-1956 -- 3 typed letters signed
      - Gilman, Lawrence (Box 1, Folder 13)
        1938 Mar 24 -- autograph letter signed (scrapbook)
      - Glanville-Hicks, Peggy (Box 1, Folder 13)
        No year Oct 30 -- typed letter signed
      - Glowacki, John (Box 1, Folder 13)
        1959 Mar 10 -- autograph letter signed (scrapbook)
      - Goeb, Roger (Box 1, Folder 13)
        No date -- typed letter
        See also: American Composers Alliance; Bard College
      - González, Bernardo Sergio (Box 1, Folder 13)
        1959 Mar 7 -- autograph letter signed
      - Goodrich, Chauncey W. (Box 1, Folder 13)
        1929 Feb 26 -- typed letter signed
      - Goodrich, Wallace (Box 1, Folder 13)
        1942 Jun 30 -- autograph letter signed
      - Gordon, Jacques (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - Goslee, George (Box 1, Folder 13)
        1939 Feb 22 -- card
      - Gottlieb, Marc (Box 1, Folder 14)
        1964 Feb 10 -- card
        See also: Claremont String Quartet
      - Grabino, Harold (Box 1, Folder 14)
        1965 Jul 16 -- typed letter signed
      - Grant, William Parks (Box 1, Folder 14)
        1949 Mar 28 -- card (scrapbook)
      - Gray, Pat (Box 1, Folder 14)
        No year Feb 19 -- autograph letter signed
      - Green, Ray (Box 1, Folder 14)
        See: American Music Center, Inc.
      - Gregg, David A. (Box 1, Folder 14)
        1957-1958 -- 2 typed letters signed
      - Gregg, Sally (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - Gregory Joseph, Sister, C.S.J. (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - Grentzer, Rose Marie (Box 1, Folder 14)
        1960 Sep 21 -- typed letter (carbon)
      - Griswold, Dick (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - Grossman, George (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - Grumman, Ellsworth (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - Grunewald, Mrs. M.E. (Box 1, Folder 14)
        See: Silvermine Chamber Music Center
      - Gunn, Glenn Dillard (Box 1, Folder 14)
        1944 Apr 10 -- typed letter signed (scrapbook)
      - Gunstead, Mary Lee (Box 1, Folder 14)
        1947 Jul 31 -- typed letter signed
      - Hadcock, Mary (Mrs. Peter) (Box 1, Folder 14)
        1964 Feb 6 -- typed letter signed (carbon)
      - Hadcock, Peter (Box 1, Folder 14)
        1964 Feb 17 -- typed letter signed (carbon)
      - Haight, Rebecca (Box 1, Folder 14)
        1938; No year Jan 22 -- 2 autograph letters signed (1-scrapbook)
      - Hall, David (Box 1, Folder 14)
        See: Composers Recordings, Inc.
      - Hanson, Howard (Box 1, Folder 14)
        1925-1929; 1951-1955 -- 7 typed letters signed
        1925; No date -- 3 telegrams (1-scrapbook)
      - Happ, Eugene (Box 1, Folder 14)
        1950 Jan 26; No date -- 2 autograph letters signed
      - Harap, Henry (Box 1, Folder 15)
        1938 Apr 9 -- typed letter signed (scrapbook)
      - Harris, Erdman (Box 1, Folder 15)
        1958-1960 -- 2 autograph letters signed (1-scrapbook)
      - Harris, Roy (Box 1, Folder 15)
        1938; 1965 -- 2 typed letters signed
      - Hart, Sarah (Box 1, Folder 15)
        [1958] -- 5 autograph letters signed
      - Haverlin, Carl (Box 1, Folder 15)
        See: Broadcast Music, Inc.
      - Haussermann, John W., Jr. (Box 1, Folder 15)
        1936 Nov 17 -- typed letter signed (scrapbook)
      - Hawthorne, Joseph (Box 1, Folder 15)
        1952 Apr 21 -- typed letter signed
      - Hazelwood, John A. (Box 1, Folder 15)
        1965 May 28 -- typed letter signed
      - Heimsath, Leda R. (Box 1, Folder 15)
        1960 Feb 24 -- typed letter signed
      - Helm, Everett (Box 1, Folder 15)
        1950 Aug 28 -- autograph letter signed (scrapbook)
      - Helps, Robert (Box 1, Folder 15)
        No year Nov 8 -- typed letter signed
      - Herrmann, Karl-Albrecht (Box 1, Folder 15)
        1953 Sep 3 -- autograph letter signed
      - Hersey, John (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - Hewett, Maurice (Box 1, Folder 15)
        1938; 1956 -- 2 typed letters signed (1-scrapbook)
      - Hickman, J. Henry (Box 1, Folder 15)
        1963 Jan 15 -- autograph letter signed
      - Hindemith, Gertrude (Box 1, Folder 15)
        See: General Correspondence to Lois Porter
      - Hindemith, Paul (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - Hinrichsen, Walter (Box 1, Folder 15)
        See: C.F. Peters Corp.
      - Hochberg, Morris (Box 1, Folder 15)
        1943 Dec 16 -- autograph letter signed (scrapbook)
      - Hodes, Herbert and Lillian (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - Hoffmann, Jim (Box 1, Folder 15)
        1957-1959 -- 2 typed letters signed
      - Hogan, Mr. and Mrs. C.B. (Box 1, Folder 15)
        1954 Mar 17 -- telegram
      - Hollander, Anne Lesser (Box 1, Folder 15)
        1950 Aug 7 -- autograph letter signed
      - Holzer, Edwin H. (Box 1, Folder 15)
        1958 Nov 25 -- typed letter signed
      - Hopkins, James (Box 1, Folder 15)
        1962-1964 -- 2 typed letters signed
      - Howard, Lee (Box 1, Folder 15)
        See: Neighborhood Music School
      - Howerton, George (Box 1, Folder 15)
        See: Northwestern University
      - Hubicki, Taras (Box 1, Folder 15)
        1960 Aug 6 -- typed letter signed (scrapbook)
      - Hufsmith, Betty (Box 1, Folder 15)
        1958-1961 -- 2 autograph letters signed
      - Hurd, Helen (Porter) [daughter] (Box 1, Folder 15)
        1949 Jun 22 -- autograph letter signed
      - Hutchins, Agnes [cousin] (Box 1, Folder 15)
        1938 Apr 8 -- autograph letter signed (scrapbook)
      - Hutchins, Margaret [cousin] (Box 1, Folder 15)
        1943 Mar 20 -- autograph letter signed
      - Jackson, Mrs. J.D. (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - Jacobi, Frederick (Box 1, Folder 16)
        No year Apr 28 -- typed letter signed (scrapbook)
      - Jacobi, Frederick and Irene (Box 1, Folder 16)
        1938 Apr 4 -- telegram (scrapbook)
      - Jacobsen, Sascha (Box 1, Folder 16)
        No date -- telegram (scrapbook)
      - James, Philip (Box 1, Folder 16)
        1935 Mar 30 -- autograph letter signed (scrapbook)
        See also: National Institute of Arts & Letters; Society for the Publication of American Music; Century Association
      - James, Philip (Box 1, Folder 16)
        1950-1951 -- 3 typed letters signed
      - Jenkins, Walter S. (Box 1, Folder 16)
        1959 Oct 23 -- autograph letter signed
      - Johansen, Gunnar (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - Johnson, Frank M. (Box 1, Folder 16)
        1952 Jul 7 -- typed letter signed
      - Johnson, Thor (Box 1, Folder 16)
        See: Cincinnati Symphony Orchestra; Morris Tyler
      - Kaplan, David (Box 1, Folder 16)
        1949 -- 2 autograph letters signed
      - Kaplan, Elliot (Box 1, Folder 16)
        1964 May 15 -- typed letter signed
      - Katims, Milton (Box 1, Folder 16)
        See: Seattle Symphony Orchestra
      - Kaufman, Louis (Box 1, Folder 16)
        1950-1951 -- 2 typed letters signed
      - Kaufman, Louis and Annette (Box 1, Folder 16)
        1949-1962 -- 7 autograph letters signed
        1951 Feb 3 -- typed letter signed (scrapbook)
      - Kemner, Gerald E. (Box 1, Folder 16)
        1957 Nov 18 -- autograph letter signed
        1958-1966 -- 7 typed letters signed
      - Kent, Charles (Box 1, Folder 16)
        1963-1964 -- 2 typed letters signed
      - [Kerr, Harrison ?] (Box 1, Folder 16)
        1942 Jun 27 -- autograph letter signed
        See also: Arrow Music Press, Inc.
      - Keyserling, Arnold (Box 1, Folder 16)
        See: enclosures filed with letter from Anne Carnahan
      - Kiernan, Paul D. (Box 1, Folder 16)
        1966 Feb 15 -- typed letter
      - Kievman, Louis (Box 1, Folder 16)
        1956 Jan 15 -- typed letter signed
      - Kilpatrick, Jack (Box 1, Folder 16)
        1946 Jun 18 -- autograph letter signed (scrapbook)
      - Kimball, Richard A. (Box 1, Folder 16)
        See: American Academy in Rome; Century Association
      - Kirkpatrick, Elizabeth Porter (Box 1, Folder 16)
        1958 Sep 4 -- typed letter (mimeograph)
      - Kirkpatrick, Ralph (Box 1, Folder 16)
        1960 Jul 13 -- typed letter signed
        See also: Yaddo; Century Association
      - Knight, Newell S. (Box 1, Folder 16)
        1963 Oct 18 -- typed letter signed
      - Knitzer, Joseph (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - Knox, Harry (Box 1, Folder 16)
        1965 Apr 14 -- card
      - Kohs, Ellis B. (Box 1, Folder 17)
        1942-1959 -- 3 typed letters signed (1-scrapbook)
      - Konetchy, Ronald (Box 1, Folder 17)
        1955 Jan 18 -- typed letter signed
      - Korn, Richard. See also: Yaddo (Box 1, Folder 17)
        1960 May 3 -- typed letter signed
      - Koussevitsky, Serge (Box 1, Folder 17)
        1942 Dec 10 -- typed letter signed (scrapbook)
        See also: American-Soviet Music Society
      - Kozlenko, William (Box 1, Folder 17)
        1935-1936 -- 2 typed letters signed (scrapbook)
      - Kramer, Tosca Berger (Box 1, Folder 17)
        1958 Jul 15 -- autograph letter signed
      - Kranz, Peter (Box 1, Folder 17)
        1965 Jan 7 -- typed letter signed
      - Kreuz, Julien (Box 1, Folder 17)
        1931; No year Jul 16 -- 2 autograph letters signed (scrapbook)
      - Kroll, William (Box 1, Folder 17)
        1943 -- 2 typed letters signed (1-scrapbook)
      - Kubie, Lawrence S. (Box 1, Folder 17)
        1938 Apr 5 -- typed letter signed (scrapbook)
      - Labunski, Felix R. (Box 1, Folder 17)
        1945 Feb 22 -- typed letter signed
      - Lam, Jennette (Box 1, Folder 17)
        1960 Mar 10 -- autograph letter signed
      - Lamb, Norman (Box 1, Folder 17)
      - La Montaine, John (Box 1, Folder 17)
        No date [c.1960?] -- 3 typed letters signed
      - Lange, Hans (Box 1, Folder 17)
        1937; 1943 -- 2 typed letters signed (scrapbook)
      - Langille, Edward D. (Box 1, Folder 17)
        1952 Feb 19 -- autograph letter signed
      - La Plante, Rita (Box 1, Folder 17)
        1949 Jul 18 -- typed letter signed
      - Laudenslager, Harold (Box 1, Folder 17)
        1958 Oct 3 -- typed letter signed
      - Layton, Billy Jim (Box 1, Folder 17)
        1949-1966 -- 6 autograph letters signed
      - Lee, Henry N. (Box 2, Folder 18)
        1963 May 7 -- typed letter signed
      - Leonard, Clair (Box 2, Folder 18)
        1938 Sep 8 -- autograph letter signed
      - Le Roy, Rene (Box 2, Folder 18)
        1935 Apr 13 -- autograph letter signed (scrapbook)
      - Lessard, John (Box 2, Folder 18)
        1966 Feb 26 -- autograph letter signed
      - Leufeuski, Gunter (Box 2, Folder 18)
        1931 Jul 21 -- typed letter signed (scrapbook)
      - Lewin, Frank (Box 2, Folder 18)
        1965-1966 -- 2 typed letters signed
        For related material, see: Catgut Acoustical Society
      - Lewis, John M. (Box 2, Folder 18)
        1946-1949 -- 2 typed letters signed
      - Lewis, Ward (Box 2, Folder 18)
        1953 Aug 7 -- autograph letter signed
      - Lieberson, Goddard (Box 2, Folder 18)
      - Liepman, Klaus (Box 2, Folder 18)
        See: Massachusetts Institute of Technology
      - Lindstrom, C.E. (Box 2, Folder 18)
        1932 Jun 17 -- typed letter signed (scrapbook)
      - Lines, Peggy (Box 2, Folder 18)
      - Limpkin, Arthur Bennett (Box 2, Folder 18)
        1965 Feb 7; No date -- 3 autograph letters signed (1-scrapbook)
      - Llewellyn, Ernest (Box 2, Folder 18)
        1956 May 3 -- autograph letter signed
      - Lobb, Nancy (Box 2, Folder 18)
        No year Feb 25 -- autograph letter signed
      - Locke, Arthur Ware (Box 2, Folder 18)
        1952 Mar 12 -- autograph letter signed
      - Lockwood, Normand (Box 2, Folder 18)
        1950-1960 -- 10 typed letters signed
      - Loeffler, Alfred T. (Box 2, Folder 19)
        1960 Jul 7 -- autograph letter signed
      - Loeffler, Martha (Mrs. Alfred T.) (Box 2, Folder 19)
        1964 Oct 27 -- autograph letter signed
      - Lopatnikoff, Nikolai (Box 2, Folder 19)
        1965-1966 -- 2 autograph letters signed
        1965-1966 -- 6 typed letters signed
      - Lovell, Joan and Patricia (Box 2, Folder 19)
        1952 Aug 28 -- autograph letter signed
      - Lovett, Sidney (Box 2, Folder 19)
        1959 Jun 28 -- autograph letter signed
      - Lovett, Esther P. (Mrs. Sidney) (Box 2, Folder 19)
        1954 Jan 25 -- card
      - Luboshutz, Pierre and Genia Nemenoff (Box 2, Folder 19)
        1956 Nov 6 -- typed letter signed
      - Lucier, Alvin (Box 2, Folder 19)
        1958-1960 -- 3 autograph letters signed
        1963 Feb 12 -- typed letter signed
      - Luening, Otto (Box 2, Folder 19)
        1949 Feb 16 -- typed letter signed
        1961 Sep 7 -- card
        See also: Yaddo; American Composers Alliance
      - Luening, Otto and Ethel (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - [Lundi, William ?] (Box 2, Folder 19)
        1956 Dec 23 -- autograph letter signed
      - Lutton, C.E. (Box 2, Folder 19)
        1949 Dec 3 -- typed letter signed (scrapbook)
      - Lyman, Tino (Ramsey) (Box 2, Folder 19)
        1959 Feb 7 -- autograph letter
      - MacArthur, Bill (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - MacColl, Hugh F. (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - McCollin, Frances (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - McCollister, Betty (Mrs. Edwin) (Box 2, Folder 19)
        1966 Apr 8 -- autograph letter signed
        1965 -- 3 typed letters signed
      - McGonagle, John J., Jr. (Box 2, Folder 19)
        1965 Sep 27 -- autograph letter signed
        1965 -- 2 typed letters signed
      - McGregor, Ruth (Mrs. Rumsey M.) (Box 2, Folder 19)
        See: The Chapin School
      - McKay, George Frederick (Box 2, Folder 19)
        1964 Dec 10 -- typed letter signed
      - MacKinnon, Robert (Box 2, Folder 19)
        1959 Feb 16 -- autograph letter signed
        1958-1959 -- 2 typed letters signed
      - McKinley, Carl (Box 2, Folder 19)
        1951; 1959 -- 2 typed letters signed
      - McMahon, Joseph H. (Box 2, Folder 19)
        1966 Aug 6 -- typed letter signed
      - McVey, William M. (Box 2, Folder 19)
        1964 Feb 22 -- autograph letter signed
        1966; No date -- 2 typed letters signed
        See also: Century Association
      - Magidoff, Nila (Box 2, Folder 20)
        [c. 1959] -- autograph letter signed
      - Mallon, John (Box 2, Folder 20)
        1959 Aug 5 -- typed letter signed
      - Mallow, Barbara Stein (Box 2, Folder 20)
        1962 Oct 18 -- autograph letter signed
      - Mann, Michael (Box 2, Folder 20)
        1952 Aug 16 -- typed letter signed
      - Matthai, Charlotte Parker (Box 2, Folder 20)
      - Melcher, Patricia (Box 2, Folder 20)
        1962 Nov 18 -- typed letter (copy)
      - Mele, Frank (Box 2, Folder 20)
        1950 Nov 28 -- typed letter signed
      - Merrell, Alice Allen (Box 2, Folder 20)
      - Merrill, Winifred (Box 2, Folder 20)
        [1944?] -- 2 typed letters signed
      - Metcalf, Mary (Box 2, Folder 20)
      - Meyer, Henry (Box 2, Folder 20)
        1950 Dec 19 -- typed letter signed (scrapbook)
      - Moe, Henry Allen (Box 2, Folder 20)
        1965 Feb 24 -- autograph letter signed
        1942-1964 -- 4 typed letters signed
        See also: American Composers Alliance; Yaddo; Guggenheim Foundation; Yale; Century Association
      - Moldavan, Nicholas (Box 2, Folder 20)
        No date -- 2 autograph letters signed (scrapbook)
      - Monks, Ann (Box 2, Folder 20)
        No year Oct 9; No date -- 2 autograph letters signed (1-scrapbook)
      - Moore, Douglas (Box 2, Folder 21)
        1952-1963 -- 4 typed letters signed
        See also: Yale; Columbia University. Alice M. Ditson Fund; Century Association
      - [Moore, Douglas ?] (Box 2, Folder 21)
        No year Sep 22 -- card
      - Moore, Earl V. (Box 2, Folder 21)
        1951; 1965 -- 2 typed letters signed (1-scrapbook)
        See also: National Association of Schools of Music
      - Morris, Franklin (Box 2, Folder 21)
        1960 Apr ? -- autograph letter signed
      - Morris, Harold (Box 2, Folder 21)
        1938 Apr 14 -- autograph letter signed (scrapbook)
      - [Morris, Hower, Jr. ?] (Box 2, Folder 21)
        1938 Apr 4 -- autograph letter signed (scrapbook)
      - Morton, Lawrence (Box 2, Folder 21)
        See: American Composers Alliance
      - Moseley, J.O.B. (Box 2, Folder 21)
        1949 Nov 28 -- typed letter signed
      - Muller, J.P. (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Murdock, Kenneth (Box 2, Folder 21)
        1958 Nov 25 -- autograph letter signed
        1944 May 13 -- typed letter signed
      - [Nathan, Robert ?] (Box 2, Folder 21)
        [1938 Apr]; No date -- 2 autograph letters signed (scrapbook)
      - Nathan, Robert (Box 2, Folder 21)
        1935 Apr 9 -- telegram
      - Naumburg, Walter W. (Box 2, Folder 21)
        1942 Jun 27 -- autograph letter signed (scrapbook)
      - Nee, Thomas (Box 2, Folder 21)
        1960-1963 -- 3 autograph letters signed
        1964 Feb 1 -- autograph letter signed (carbon)
        See also: New Hampshire Music Festival
      - Newell, Paul (Box 2, Folder 21)
        1949 Apr 25 -- telegram
      - Nield, Betty and Walter (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Nolte, Mimi (Box 2, Folder 21)
        1949 Jul 26 -- autograph letter signed
      - Noss, Luther (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - O'Neill, Alice Little (Box 2, Folder 22)
        1938 Apr 11 -- autograph letter signed (scrapbook)
      - Ortel, Noyde (Mrs. William C.G.) (Box 2, Folder 22)
        1965 May 29 -- autograph letter signed
      - Palestrant, Stephen (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Palmer, Robert M. (Box 2, Folder 22)
        1938 Apr 9 -- autograph letter signed (scrapbook)
      - Parisot, Aldo (Box 2, Folder 22)
        [c. 1950] -- 5 autograph letters signed
      - Partch, Harry (Box 2, Folder 22)
        1958 Dec 14 -- autograph letter signed
      - Payment, Mrs. (Box 2, Folder 22)
        1940 Feb 24 -- telegram (scrapbook)
      - Peach, Bernard (Box 2, Folder 22)
        1960 Jun 30 -- typed letter signed
      - Pelz, William (Box 2, Folder 22)
        1952 -- 2 typed letters signed
      - Perkins, Francis D. (Box 2, Folder 22)
        1925 May 1 -- autograph letter signed
      - Pervini, Nicholas J. (Box 2, Folder 22)
        1963 May 6 -- autograph letter signed
      - Phelps, Frances (Box 2, Folder 22)
        1949 Oct 1 -- typed letter signed
      - Pierce, Esther (Box 2, Folder 22)
        1943 Feb 28 -- autograph letter signed
      - Pinney, Alexander (Box 2, Folder 22)
        See: Century Association
      - Pisk, Paul A. (Box 2, Folder 22)
        1941 Jan 12 -- autograph letter signed (scrapbook)
      - Pleasants, Virginia (Box 2, Folder 22)
        1965-1966 -- 5 typed letters signed
      - Pleasants, Virginia and Bill (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Polk, Louise Burr (Box 2, Folder 22)
        1938 Mar 3 -- autograph letter signed (scrapbook)
      - Porter, Frank Chamberlin [father] (Box 2, Folder 23)
        1943-1944; No date -- 5 autograph letters signed (1-scrapbook)
        1945 Oct 16 -- card (scrapbook)
      - Porter, Lillian (Mrs. Lucius) (Box 2, Folder 23)
        1953 Aug 30 -- typed letter
      - Porter, Lois (Brown) [wife] (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Porter, Lucius C. [cousin] (Box 2, Folder 23)
        1938; 1952 -- 2 typed letters signed
        1946 Sep 16 -- card
      - Porter, Lyman E. [brother] (Box 2, Folder 23)
        1938-1958 -- 7 typed letters signed (1-scrapbook)
        No year Apr 9 -- card (scrapbook)
      - Porter, Mary Q. [aunt] (Box 2, Folder 23)
        1935-1944 -- 3 autograph letters signed
        1944 Oct 2 -- card
      - Porter, William L. [son] (Box 2, Folder 23)
        1958 Sep 3 -- autograph letter signed
      - Porter, William L. and Lynn (Box 2, Folder 23)
        1958 Mar 27 -- typed letter signed
        For other family correspondence, see: section J. (early correspondence with family); section K. (Lois Porter); as well as congratulatory letters
      - Pottle, Sam (Box 2, Folder 24)
        No year Jul 15; No date -- 2 autograph letters signed
      - Preston, Richard Greeley (Box 2, Folder 24)
        1949 Sep 12 -- typed letter signed
      - Preves, Milton (Box 2, Folder 24)
        1948-1951 -- 2 autograph letters signed
        1951 -- 3 typed letters signed
      - Primrose, Dorothy (Mrs. William) (Box 2, Folder 24)
      - Primrose, William (Box 2, Folder 24)
        1948 Dec 7 -- autograph letter signed
        1948-1951 -- 2 typed letters signed